I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky You’re from
Я из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда
Russia, the city of Chelyabinsk, Ural, I realized who’s
Россия город Челябинск Урал понял кто по
nationality is
национальности
half Russian, half Armenian, you
наполовину русский наполовину армянин
take pills more often
чаще таблетки делаешь
at the moment, yes, it’s boring, there’s
на данный момент да скучно делать нечего
nothing to do in the house, I’ve remodeled everything on the computer, there’s nothing to do on the street, there’s nothing to do on the street, there’s
нечего на улице делать нечего на улице
always something to do, I’m watching, I was
Всегда есть что делать я смотрю Я
watching  the news there is that the military registration and enlistment office
смотрел новости там то военкомат
caught fire, so in short, there are some
загорелся так то короче какие-то там
factories there. So on the street you can always
заводы Так что на улице всегда можно
find something to do, go there and look,
найти себе занятие там идти и смотреть
or by chance something didn’t catch fire,
или случайно что-то не загорелось
firemen call, that’s
пожарные звонить
not it, I’m not interested in such things,
не это не я такими вещами не интересуюсь
friends, met there, talked,
друзьями встретился там пообщался
walked,
погулял
friend too  met, talked,
подруга тоже встретился пообщался
in the car, seems to have done everything, washed, cleaned,
в машине вроде все сделал помыл почистил
asks Yes,
спрашивает
there is no specific topic, I just
Да нет какой-то определенной темы просто
came purely to lift my mood
зашел чисто для поднятия настроения себе
or to get in the mood, I’m talking about such a topic, it’s
либо принятия настроения я такой теме
not for nothing that I told Dasha there are
говорю вот Я же не зря сказал Дашу на
heaps on the street. How is it that in
улице кучи есть Как так получается что в
Russia there are very  a lot of people are setting fire
России очень много людей поджигают
to military registration and enlistment offices. So
военкоматы Так
line Cabinets on the railway, factories and
лейные Шкафы на железной дороге заводы и
so on, somehow it turns out that these are
так дальше как-то получается что это
Russian people. Well, this is purely my opinion, these are
русский люди Ну это Чисто мое мнение это
the people who are deserting, those people
те люди которые дезертируют те люди
who are being sold. Also, I think you
которые продаются также я думаю вы точно
know exactly about the man who stole the
знаете про того человека который украл
helicopter mi-  8 in general, really, damn it, well, this is
вертолет ми-8 вообще реально блин ну это
your opinion, this is your opinion. I have a
ваше мнение это ваше мнение У меня
completely opposite opinion, but
абсолютно противоположное мнение но
a hero.
герой
Look, I don’t consider this person a hero,
Смотри я не считаю этого человека героя
because this is a person
так как этот человек
who didn’t know at all about what was
которые вообще не знали о том что
going to happen and they were killed by yours or whatever it is.
произойдет и их убили Ваше всу или как
Yes, this also happens  Also, these
там всу Да так бывает также также Эти
people, these same people, could eat with this person
люди эти же люди могли с этим человеком
from the same plate, drink from the same
кушать с одной тарелки пить С одной
mug, eat from the same spoon, this man
кружки есть с одной ложки Этот человек
also set him up, this man in front of me
также подставил Этот человек передо мной
fell fell just below the foot of
пал пал просто ниже ниже стопы
the plinth below the foot of this man, I don’t
плинтуса ниже стопы этого человека я не
consider
считаю
any heroes for  for you he is a hero for
каким-то там героям для вас он герой для
you he is a hero For us this is a man Yes I
вас он герой Для нас это человек Да я
consider him a [ __ ] [ __ ] Why can I
его считаю шлюхой шлюхой Почему я могу
explain because I can explain
объяснить потому что я могу объяснить
because this man sold out He
потому что этот человек продался Он
sold out just like an ordinary girl
продался так же как обычная девушка
sells her body for money to other
продает свое тело за деньги другим
men
мужика
he is in order to stop  this
он для того чтобы остановить эту
criminal Putin’s war But
преступную путинскую войну А вот
look, Russia has money Why
посмотри У России есть деньги Почему
no one from Ukraine will fly in with a
никто из Украины не прилетит с
helicopter, why so
вертолетом почему так
from Ukraine
из Украины
I don’t know because maybe there were no
Я не знаю потому что может быть не было
such prerequisites Why are there
таких каких-то предпосылок А почему да
such prerequisites that a Russian calmly
так предпосылки что русский спокойно
flew to Ukraine So
перелетел в Украину Так
how many  for a year and a half you are not a plane, no one
сколько полтора года вы не самолет никто
has arrived in Russia,
не прилетел в России
I don’t know who the hell knows honestly, that is, it
я хрен его знает честно то есть
turns out that the Russians
получается что русские
are pulling
перетягивают
equipment to the side of Ukraine, the Ukrainians are not,
технику на сторону Украины украинцы нет
but Look, this is one of some
но Смотри это один из из каких-то
millions of people who sold, he didn’t
миллионов человек которые продал не
sell,
продался
he didn’t do it for ideological reasons
не он из идейных соображений сделал
Why not  sold out, they offered him 500
Почему не продался ему предложили 500
thousand bucks Well, it’s like a reward
тысяч бачей Ну это как вознаграждение
later Yes, a bonus
потом Да бонус
if the reward hadn’t been offered, it would
если бы вознаграждение не предложили
have been more difficult,
сложнее было
look, but it’s funny for
смотри но прикол
him now some other side,
сейчас ему какая-нибудь другая сторона
being with you in Ukraine,
будучи находящийся он у вас в Украине
the other side will offer him more than what
ему другая сторона предложит больше чем
Ukraine offered, it’s
предложила Украина
cool
прикольно
because the person
потому что человек
is him  He doesn’t need to fly for a
ему Ему же не надо сейчас летать на
million now, no one will let him in.
миллион никто не будет пускать Наверное
He’s probably still living and resting in peace, the media, and
он все живёт отдыхает уже спокойно СМИ и
enjoying life more and more, and that is,
всё короче кайфует жизни да то есть
look, it turns out that after all, we understand
смотри получается что всё-таки мы поняли
what’s wrong with Ukraine. No one has flown to Ukraine in all these
да что с Украины Никто за все эти года
two years.  Russia And from Russia
два года не улетел в Россию А из России
continue Sorry interrupted continuation And
продолжай Извини перебил продолжение А
from Russia flew away Yes the kid is in Russia to
из России улетел Да пацанчик в России в
Ukraine But it turns out that then it’s serious Well,
Украину Но получается что тогда серьезно
as I’m telling you since I know,
Ну как я говорю тебе так как я знаю
maybe you don’t know something, maybe
может быть ты чего-то не знаешь может
I don’t know something, but think about it
быть чего-то не знаю я но Прикинь может
maybe there are the same people who also
быть есть такие же люди которые также
jumped over, maybe it’s just if Russia has
перемахнули может просто если у России
so much money
столько денег
Did she also announce
Неужели она мне объявила также
a reward to me? all the Ukrainian pilots
вознаграждение все украинские пилоты
flew to Russia
улетели в России
and the Russian one flew away, look
а российский улетел смотри
I don’t know honestly how to answer this
Я не знаю честно как ответить на этот
question since I’m not entirely informed so as
вопрос так как я не совсем осведомлен
not to end up
чтобы не оказаться дурачком в твоих
I may have already turned out to be a fool in your eyes, but
глазах возможно я уже таким оказался но
I don’t know how to answer this question, but
я не знаю как ответить на этот вопрос но
I’ll just say something slightly different. Look,
я просто скажу чуть-чуть другое Смотри
now Russia is not really fighting, but
сейчас же Россия воюет не совсем но
almost no longer from Ukraine, right. And with whom,
почти уже не с Украины правильно А с кем
America? That’s for sure. She’s
с Америкой Это точно Она
just Ukraine.  they will come out with American
просто Украина выйдут американским
weapons and NATO
оружием на и натовски
Iranian North Korean will now
иранским северокорейским сейчас будет
fight Russia Russia is still fighting
воевать Россия Россия до сих пор воюет
with its weapons, look if
со своим оружием смотри если бы за
not one would have gone for Ukraine
Украину не пошли бы ни один
like that Come on Yes come on Well look They would have taken
так Давай Да давай Ну смотри Взяли бы
Ukraine But they took it Agree Yes, but it
Украину Но взяли Согласись Да а
turns out that is, look Russia thought
получается то есть смотри Россия думала
that now he will attack this like a gopnik
что сейчас нападет на вот это как гопник
in a gateway, I think now he will attack an
в подворотне думаю сейчас нападет на
unarmed boy, but it turns out that the kid is a
безружного пацана а оказывается пацану
good uncle, I gave pistols and machine guns, a
хороший дяди дали я пистолеты и автоматы
grenade, and the gopnik got stars, that
гранату Да и гопник получил звездюлей то
is, look, now you are really complaining
есть смотри ты сейчас реально жалуешься
that weapons helped Ukraine Well, you are
что Украине помогли оружие Ну ты ты
really making excuses And if  if only
реально оправдываешься И если бы если бы
it’s funny, such a thrill, just if if, what
это смешно такая кайф просто если бы
can you do without someone
если бы то что вы можете без кого-то
or what’s the difference, look, we’re giving
либо вообще какая разница смотри мы даем
you
вам
Ukraine Here
Украина
in the gateway,
Вот в подворот
this is when we agreed Let’s go
это когда мы договорились Давай выйдем
one-on-one
один на один
no situation at all,
вообще никакой ситуации
you say Russia gopniks, I’m a gopnik
ты говоришь Россия гопники я гопник Да
Yes, here I go, you’re there, you’ve got an
вот я иду ты там такой там заряженный у
iPhone charged there, and it’s got a pocket full of money.
тебя там iPhone и он там денег полный
I come and say, Hey, give me
карман Я прихожу говорю Слышь дай ко мне
the [ __ ] of a ship, and you say, Hey,
на суда все нахуй а ты говоришь Слышь
guys, come here. What can you do? And
пацаны иди сюда А сам что можешь А сам
what can you do, guys, look like this?  so
что вот а пацаны вот так смотри так
look, it’s not America that’s hitting the vases now, but the
смотри вазы бьют сейчас не Америка да а
Ukrainians are hitting you. Just look, these
украинцы бьют вас Да просто смотри эти
boys are coming up to play, look, kid, we
пацаны подходят играть смотри пацанчик
won’t get out, but you’re
мы вылезать не будем но на тебе
normal, in short, too. Weapons so you
нормальный короче тоже Оружие чтобы ты
give him a kick in the ass and you kick
дал ему надрал задницу и ты надираешь
this gopnik’s ass. The truth is, it’s
этому гопнику задницу Правда надирает же
not America that’s kicking you  Ukraine is kicking you with
вам не Америка надирает вам Украина с
American weapons Yes, vegetables
американским оружием Да овощи Да с
Yes, with the help, right and what And it
помощью правильно а что А на безоружного
was good to attack an unarmed person, that is, they wanted
хорошо было нападать то есть хотели
to attack and there is a lox Without weapons Now I’m
напасти а идёт лошок Без оружия Сейчас я
shorter than him,
его короче
plus a subscriber Like
плюс подписчица Поставьте лайк
If only if I love so much If only damn
Если бы если бы я так люблю Если бы блин
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube is driving us into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кардиорке в
shadow ban through cardio and a very rich appearance is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы
because there is little experience and stars
потому для то чтобы мало опыта и звездок
peak pushchina right at a time and there are attempts there in a
пик пущица прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Cream video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we would give you attractions
информация и мы бы вынес вам аттраматы
according  stylish
по стильной
operational stars are laid down to
оперативной звездок заложено
show you the YouTube word of Ukraine
покажем вам YouTube слово Украине